Guide to the Language Resource Center collection, circa 1963-1983.
Language Resource Center collection,
- Reel-to-reel tape recordings
  - Cornell material
    - Spring Evening, Undated; TR-12170 (Box 23)
      LRC #: CTX 1
    - Cantonese 312 Readings Spring Evening, Undated; TR-12171 (Box 23)
      LRC #: CTX 2
    - Chinese Folk Songs, Undated; TR-12172 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTF 1
    - Chinese Folk Songs, Undated; TR-12173 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTF 10
    - Chinese Folk Songs, Undated; TR-12174 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTF 11
    - Chinese Folk Songs, Undated; TR-12175 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTF 2
    - Chinese Folk Songs, Undated; TR-12176 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTF 3
    - Chinese Folk Songs, Undated; TR-12177 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTF 4
    - Chinese Folk Songs, Undated; TR-12178 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTF 5
    - Chinese Folk Songs, Undated; TR-12179 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTF 6
    - Chinese Folk Songs, Undated; TR-12180 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTF 7
    - Chinese Folk Songs, Undated; TR-12181 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTF 8
    - Chinese Folk Songs, Undated; TR-12182 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTF 9
    - Speak Cantonese Book 1, Undated; TR-12183 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTL 1
    - Speak Cantonese Book 1, Undated; TR-12184 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTL 10
    - Speak Cantonese Book 1, Undated; TR-12185 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTL 2
    - Speak Cantonese Book 1, Undated; TR-12186 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTL 3
    - Speak Cantonese Book 1, Undated; TR-12187 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTL 4
    - Speak Cantonese Book 1, Undated; TR-12188 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTL 5
    - Speak Cantonese Book 1, Undated; TR-12189 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTL 6
    - Speak Cantonese Book 1, Undated; TR-12190 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTL 7
    - Speak Cantonese Book 1, Undated; TR-12191 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTL 8
    - Speak Cantonese Book 1, Undated; TR-12192 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTL 9
    - Read Chinese, Book 2, Undated; TR-12193 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTR 2.1
    - Read Chinese, Book 2, Undated; TR-12194 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTR 2.2
    - Read Chinese, Book 2, Undated; TR-12195 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTR 2.3
    - Read Chinese, Book 2, Undated; TR-12196 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTR 2.4
    - Read Chinese, Book 2, Undated; TR-12197 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTR 2.5
    - Read Chinese, Book 2, Undated; TR-12198 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTR 2.6
    - Read Chinese, Book 2, Undated; TR-12199 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTR 2.7
    - Read Chinese, Book 2, Undated; TR-12200 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTR 2.8
    - Read Chinese, Book 2, Undated; TR-12201 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTR 2.9
    - Read Chinese, Book 2, Undated; TR-12202 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTR 2.10
    - Read Chinese, Book 2, Undated; TR-12203 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTR 2.11
    - Read Chinese, Book 2, Undated; TR-12204 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTR 2.12
    - Read Chinese, Book 2, Undated; TR-12205 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTR 2.13
    - Read Chinese, Book 2, Undated; TR-12206 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTR 2.14
    - Read Chinese, Book 2, Undated; TR-12207 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTR 2.15
    - Cantonese: Supplementary Vocab. and Idioms, Undated; TR-12208 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTV 1.1
    - Cantonese: Supplementary Vocab. and Idioms, Undated; TR-12209 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTV 1.2
    - Cantonese: Supplementary Vocab. and Idioms, Undated; TR-12210 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTV 2.1
    - Cantonese: Supplementary Vocab. and Idioms, Undated; TR-12211 (Box 24)
      LRC #: CTV 2.2
    - Cantonese, Undated; TR-12212 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTT 1
    - Cantonese, Undated; TR-12213 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTT 10
    - Cantonese, Undated; TR-12214 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTT 11
    - Cantonese, Undated; TR-12215 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTT 12
    - Cantonese, Undated; TR-12216 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTT 13
    - Cantonese, Undated; TR-12217 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTT 14
    - Cantonese, Undated; TR-12218 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTT 15
    - Cantonese, Undated; TR-12219 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTT 16
    - Cantonese, Undated; TR-12220 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTT 17
    - Cantonese, Undated; TR-12221 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTT 2
    - Cantonese, Undated; TR-12222 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTT 3
    - Cantonese, Undated; TR-12223 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTT 4
    - Cantonese, Undated; TR-12224 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTT 5
    - Cantonese, Undated; TR-12225 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTT 6
    - Cantonese, Undated; TR-12226 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTT 7
    - Cantonese, Undated; TR-12227 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTT 8
    - Cantonese, Undated; TR-12228 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTT 9
    - Cantonese Supplementary Conversations, Undated; TR-12229 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTS 1
    - Cantonese Supplementary Conversations, Undated; TR-12230 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTS 2
    - Cantonese Supplementary Conversations, Undated; TR-12231 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTS 3
    - Cantonese Supplementary Conversations, Undated; TR-12232 (Box 25)
      LRC #: CTS 4
    - Beginning Javanese, Undated; TR-12233 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JV 1
    - Beginning Javanese, Undated; TR-12234 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JV 10
    - Beginning Javanese, Undated; TR-12235 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JV 11
    - Beginning Javanese, Undated; TR-12236 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JV 2
    - Beginning Javanese, Undated; TR-12237 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JV 3
    - Beginning Javanese, Undated; TR-12238 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JV 4
    - Beginning Javanese, Undated; TR-12239 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JV 5
    - Beginning Javanese, Undated; TR-12240 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JV 6
    - Beginning Javanese, Undated; TR-12241 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JV 7
    - Beginning Javanese, Undated; TR-12242 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JV 8
    - Beginning Javanese, Undated; TR-12243 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JV 9
    - Javanese Exam, Undated; TR-12244 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVE 1
    - Supplementary Lesson 1, 3, and 4, Undated; TR-12245 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 1
    - Supplementary Lesson 13 (Beginning), 14 (End), Undated; TR-12246 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 10
    - Supplementary Lesson 13 (from 15 to 47b), Undated; TR-12247 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 11
    - Supplementary Lesson 13 (Ending), Undated; TR-12248 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 12
    - Supplementary Lesson 14 (Part A), Undated; TR-12249 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 13
    - Supplementary Lesson 14 (Part B and Beginning of C), Undated; TR-12250 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 14
    - Supplementary Lesson 14 (56b to 78a), Undated; TR-12251 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 15
    - Supplementary Lesson 15 (Beginning), Undated; TR-12252 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 16
    - Supplementary Lesson, Undated; TR-12253 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 17
    - Supplementary Lesson, Undated; TR-12254 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 18
    - Supplementary Lesson 17, 18, 19, 20, Undated; TR-12255 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 19
    - Supplementary Lesson 5 and 6 parts A and B, Undated; TR-12256 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 2
    - Supplementary Lesson 24 A, B, C, Undated; TR-12257 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 20
    - Supplementary Lesson 24 D, 23, Undated; TR-12258 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 21
    - Supplementary Lesson 6 parts C and D, Undated; TR-12259 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 3
    - Supplementary Lesson 7, Undated; TR-12260 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 4
    - Supplementary Lesson 9, Undated; TR-12261 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 5
    - Supplementary Lesson 10, Undated; TR-12262 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 6
    - Supplementary Lesson 11 (Beginning), Undated; TR-12263 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 7
    - Supplementary Lesson 11 (Ending), Undated; TR-12264 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 8
    - Supplementary Lesson 12, Undated; TR-12265 (Box 25)
      LRC #: JVJ 9
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12266; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 1A
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12267; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 2B.1
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12268; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 2B.2
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12269; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 2C
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12270; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 3A
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12271; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 4A
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12272; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 4B.1
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12273; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 4B.2
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12274; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 5A
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12275; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 5B
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12276 (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 6
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12277; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 21
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12278; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 21A.1
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12279; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 21A.2
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12280; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 23
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12281; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 7A.1
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12282; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 7A.2
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12283; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 7B.1
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12284; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 7B.2
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12285; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 7C.1
    - Javanese Supplement, Undated; TR-12286; Cornell DMLL (Box 26)
      LRC #: JVS 7C.2
    - Old Church Slavonic, Undated; TR-12287 (Box 26)
      LRC #: SLO 1
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12288 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 1
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12289 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 10
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12290 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 11
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12291 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 12
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12292 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 13
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12293 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 14
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12294 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 15
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12295 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 16
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12296 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 17
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12297 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 18
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12298 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 19
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12299 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 2
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12300 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 20
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12301 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 21
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12302 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 22
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12303 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 23
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12304 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 24
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12305 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 25
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12306 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 26
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12307 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 27
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12308 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 28
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12309 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 29
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12310 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 3
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12311 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 30
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12312 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 31
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12313 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 32
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12314 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 33
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12315 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 34
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12316 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 35
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12317 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 36
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12318 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 37
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12319 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 38
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12320 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 39
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12321 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 4
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12322 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 40
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12323 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 41
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12324 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 42
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12325 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 43
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12326 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 44
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12327 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 45
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12328 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 46
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12329 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 5
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12330 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 6
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12331 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 7
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12332 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 8
    - Spanish - Agard, Undated; TR-12333 (Box 27)
      LRC #: S 9
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12334 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 13.3
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12335 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 13.4
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12336 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 13.5
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12337 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 13.6
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12338 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 13.7
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12339 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 13.8
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12340 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 14.1
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12341 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 14.2
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12342 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 14.3
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12343 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 14.4
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12344 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 15.1
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12345 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 15.2
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12346 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 15.3
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12347 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 15.4
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12348 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 15.5
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12349 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 16.1
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12350 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 16.2
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12351 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 16.3
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12352 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 16.4
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12353 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 17.1
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12354 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 17.2
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12355 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 17.3
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12356 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 17.4
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12357 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 17.5
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12358 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 18.1
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12359 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 18.2
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12360 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 19.1
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12361 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 19.2
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12362 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 19.3
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12363 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 19.4
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12364 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 19.5
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12365 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 19.6
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12366 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 19.7
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12367 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 20.1
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12368 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 20.2
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12369 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 20.3
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12370 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 20.4
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12371 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 20.5
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12372 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 20.6
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12373 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 21.1
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12374 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 21.2
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12375 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 21.3
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12376 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 21.4
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12377 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 21.5
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12378 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 21.6
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12379 (Box 29)
      LRC #: IN 21.7
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12380 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 3.1
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12381 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 3.2
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12382 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 3.3
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12383 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 3.4
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12384 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 3.5
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12385 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 3.6
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12386 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 4.1
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12387 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 4.2
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12388 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 4.3
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12389 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 4.4
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12390 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 4.5
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12391 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 4.6
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12392 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 5.1
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12393 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 5.2
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12394 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 5.3
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12395 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 5.4
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12396 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 5.5
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12397 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 5.6
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12398 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 6.1
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12399 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 6.2
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12400 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 6.3
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12401 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 6.4
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12402 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 6.5
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12403 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 6.6
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12404 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 6.7
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12405 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 7.1
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12406 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 7.2
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12407 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 7.3
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12408 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 7.4
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12409 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 7.5
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12410 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 7.6
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12411 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 7.7
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12412 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 8.1
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12413 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 8.2
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12414 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 8.3
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12415 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 8.4
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12416 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 8.5
    - Tagalog, Undated; TR-12417 (Box 30)
      LRC #: TGW 8.6
    - Indonesian Examination, Undated; TR-12418 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 1
    - Indonesian Examination - Answers, Undated; TR-12419 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 1.1 Key
    - Indonesian Conversation, Undated; TR-12420 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 10
    - Indonesian Conversation, Undated; TR-12421 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 10 Key
    - Indonesian Exam, Undated; TR-12422 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 11
    - Indonesian Exam, Undated; TR-12423 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 12
    - Indonesian Exam, Undated; TR-12424 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 13
    - Indonesian Exam, Undated; TR-12425 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 14
    - Indonesian Exam, Undated; TR-12426 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 16
    - Indonesian Examination, Undated; TR-12427 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 1A
    - Indonesian Examination - Answers, Undated; TR-12428 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 1A Key
    - Indonesian - Test, Undated; TR-12429 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 1B
    - Indonesian Examination, Undated; TR-12430 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 1C
    - Indonesian Examination, Undated; TR-12431 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 1D
    - Indonesian Examination, Undated; TR-12432 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 1E
    - Indonesian Exam 3, Undated; TR-12433 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 3
    - Indonesian Exam 3 - Answers, Undated; TR-12434 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 3 Key
    - Indonesian Exam Skit, Undated; TR-12435 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 3.3
    - Beginning Indonesian, Undated; TR-12436 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 3.4
    - Indonesian Exam, Undated; TR-12437 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 3A
    - Indonesian Exam Key, Undated; TR-12438 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 3A Key
    - Indonesian Exam, Undated; TR-12439 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 3B
    - Indonesian Exam 4, Undated; TR-12440 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 4
    - Indonesian Exam 4 Key, Undated; TR-12441 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 4 Key
    - Indonesian Exam, Undated; TR-12442 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 4.2
    - Indonesian Exam Key, Undated; TR-12443 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 4.2 Key
    - Beginning Indonesian Exam, Undated; TR-12444 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 4.3
    - Beginning Indonesian Key, Undated; TR-12445 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 4.3 Key
    - Indonesian Exam 5, Undated; TR-12446 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 5
    - Indonesian Exam 5 Key, Undated; TR-12447 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 5 Key
    - Indonesian Exam 6, Undated; TR-12448 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 6
    - Indonesian Exam, Undated; TR-12449 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 6.1
    - Indonesian Exam, Undated; TR-12450 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 7.1
    - Key for Indonesian Exam, Undated; TR-12451 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 7.1 Key
    - Indonesian Exam, Undated; TR-12452 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 7.2
    - Key for Indonesian Exam, Undated; TR-12453 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 7.2 Key
    - Indonesian FALCON Final Exam, Undated; TR-12454 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 8
    - Indonesian FALCON Final Exam Key, Undated; TR-12455 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 8 Key
    - Indonesian Examination, Undated; TR-12456 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 9
    - Indonesian Examination Key, Undated; TR-12457 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INE 9 Key
    - Indonesian, Undated; TR-12458 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INI 1
    - Indonesian Interview, Undated; TR-12459 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INI 10
    - Indonesian Interview, Undated; TR-12460 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INI 14
    - Indonesian Interview, Undated; TR-12461 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INI 15
    - Indonesian Interview, Undated; TR-12462 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INI 16
    - Indonesian Interview, Undated; TR-12463 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INI 2
    - Indonesian Interview, Undated; TR-12464 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INI 3
    - Indonesian Interview, Undated; TR-12465 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INI 4
    - Indonesian Interview, Undated; TR-12466 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INI 5
    - Indonesian Interview, Undated; TR-12467 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INI 6
    - Indonesian Interview, Undated; TR-12468 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INI 7
    - Indonesian Interview, Undated; TR-12469 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INI 8
    - Indonesian Interview, Undated; TR-12470 (Box 31)
      LRC #: INI 9
    - Vietnamese Pronunciation, Undated; TR-12471; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: VP 2
    - Vietnamese Pronunciation, Undated; TR-12472; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: VP 3
    - Vietnamese Pronunciation, Undated; TR-12473; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: VP 4
    - Vietnamese Pronunciation, Undated; TR-12474; FSI (Box 35)
      LRC #: VP 5
    - Vietnamese Lesson 1, Undated; TR-12475 (Box 35)
      LRC #: VO 1
    - Vietnamese Lesson 2, Undated; TR-12476 (Box 35)
      LRC #: VO 2
    - Vietnamese Lesson 3, Undated; TR-12477 (Box 35)
      LRC #: VO 3
    - Vietnamese Lesson 10, Undated; TR-12478 (Box 35)
      LRC #: VO 10
    - Vietnamese Lesson 12, Undated; TR-12479 (Box 35)
      LRC #: VO 12
    - Vietnamese Lesson 4, Undated; TR-12480 (Box 35)
      LRC #: VO 4
    - Vietnamese Lesson 5, Undated; TR-12481 (Box 35)
      LRC #: VO 5
    - Vietnamese Lesson 6, Undated; TR-12482 (Box 35)
      LRC #: VO 6
    - Vietnamese Lesson 8, Undated; TR-12483 (Box 35)
      LRC #: VO 8
    - Vietnamese Lesson 9, Undated; TR-12484 (Box 35)
      LRC #: VO 9
    - Vietnamese Reader Master 1, Undated; TR-12485 (Box 35)
      LRC #: VRT 1
    - Vietnamese Reader Master 2, Undated; TR-12486 (Box 35)
      LRC #: VRT 2
    - Vietnamese Reader Master 3, Undated; TR-12487 (Box 35)
      LRC #: VRT 3
    - Northern Vietnamese Master 10, Undated; TR-12488 (Box 35)
    - Northern Vietnamese Master 5, Undated; TR-12489 (Box 35)
    - Northern Vietnamese Master 6, Undated; TR-12490 (Box 35)